We sell a sustainable growth platform for gyms.
We do $4 million revenue.
We'd like to be at 10 in two years.
It's formerly top line, right?
What's profit?
2.2.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, it's just like, you have to get to like, you know, 300,000 a month notes.
Right.
You just get the volume.
Yeah.
So what breaks when you scale the volume?
Why can't we do more?
And the web team's starting to kind of scream a little bit.
Okay.
You know, so probably some bandwidth there, like, do I stop and fix that now or do we
just build the plane as we fly and just keep charging?
I build capacity.
You're profitable.
You're pulling off the gas right now.
I'm kind of feeling, right?
Is that you're not like, I'm going to go balls to wall right now.
I think this kind of goes for, I'm really like, how can I make this happen?
Building capacity will keep your ethics high.
We have to either choose to sacrifice profit or reputation.
So if you're at a capacity constraint, you either have to reach into your bottom line
and build capacity, or you add to your bottom line by increasing demand and having something
takes a hit.
And so it's likely going to be your metrics or reputation.